Billy Byers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Full Scores (Box 1-35)
  - Lane, Abbe
    - Celebrity medley: vaudeville 1977, Includes: "Mimi;" "Cuban Pete;" "They can’t take that away from me;" "Puttin’ on the Ritz;" "The way you look tonight;" "Swanee;" "Mammy."; Laid in: piano conductor, violin and percussion parts on transparency. (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Dance: ten, looks: three, Laid in: piano conductor, violin and percussion parts on transparency. (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Happy together, Laid in: piano conductor, violin and percussion parts on transparency. (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Never can say goodbye, Laid in: piano conductor and percussion parts on transparency. (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Opening ‘77: vaudeville 1977, Includes "Fascinatin’ rhythm."; Laid in: piano conductor, violin and percussion parts on transparency. (Box-folder 15/16)
    - Shangri-La bows, Piano conductor, violin and percussion parts on transparency only; arranged by Nan Schwartz. (Box-folder 34/1)
  - The Late Liz: #5283: Dick Ross & Associates
    - [Miscellaneous cues], Includes: Reward m11-01; Strangers in the night m-62; The rent is paid m-63; Committing sideways m-72. (Box-folder 15/17)
  - Lawrence, Carol see Goulet, Robert/Carol Lawrence
  - Lawrence, Steve see Steve and Eydie
  - Norman Lear, TV and Film, 1980
    - [Miscellaneous cues], Includes: Tumblin’ buddies; Main title 60; Main title 90; King of the hill. (Box-folder 15/18)
  - Lee, Peggy
    - Brother Love’s traveling salvation show: vaudeville, arranged, June 29, 1969 (Box-folder 15/19)
  - Lennon Sisters see ABC 25th anniversary
  - Lewis, Jerry
    - Anything goes: vaudeville 1979 (Box-folder 15/20)
    - As time goes by (Box-folder 15/21)
    - Fanfare - What the world needs now: muscular dystrophy telethon, 1979 (Box-folder 15/22)
    - For once in my life: Tonight Show (Box-folder 16/1)
    - A now and later love: Jerry Lewis Prod., Aug. 28, 1966 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Smile - Mexicali: muscular dystrophy telethon, 1979 Smile - disco: muscular dystrophy telethon - ‘79 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Spinning wheel (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Sweet Caroline (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Walking in the park: Jerry Lewis Prod., Aug. 23, 1966 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Without you: muscular dystrophy (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Lewis, Jerry Lee see The Music Scene
  - Limehouse, home of the blues (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Loring, Gloria
    - Higher and higher Higher and higher - fixes (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Lovell, Marilyn
    - Color my world (Box-folder 16/10)
    - I can do a trick (Box-folder 16/11)
    - Special people (Box-folder 16/12)
    - Who am I? (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Lucien, Jon
    - I’m comin’ home again: vaudeville 1975 (Box-folder 16/14)
    - I’ve got you under my skin: 1979 (Box-folder 16/15)
    - My funny Valentine: vaudeville 1979 (Box-folder 16/16)
    - Witchcraft: vaudeville 1979 (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Luft, Lorna
    - They can’t take that away from me: vaudeville arrangement 1972 (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Macho Callahan: Felicidad Films, composed by Pat Williams, July 14, 1970
    - [Miscellaneous cues], Includes: M801; M-1001; M-1002; M-1003; M-1004; M1101; M-1102; M-1201. (Box-folder 16/19)
  - MacLaine, Shirley
    - Foot and cymbal dance (opener), Found with mis-identified Music Man medley. (Box-folder 16/20)
    - [Miscellaneous cues]: tv special, 1980, Includes: End credits, good nights b.g. (Box-folder 16/21)
    - Movin’ on: tv special, 1980 (Box-folder 16/22)
    - World of ballet: tv special World of ballet, part II: tv special, 1980 (Box-folder 16/23)
  - MacLeod, Gavin see McLeod, Gavin
  - Manchester, Melissa
    - Waltzin’ the jack, Adapted from "Ballin’ the jack." (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Mancini, Henry see Newley, Anthony
  - Manhattans
    - Lean on me: vaudeville, August 1976, Includes: "Bridge over troubled water;" "Somewhere." (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Mann, Herbie see The Music Scene
  - Marieke, For Joel; appears to be part of a medley. (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Martin Show, Dean see Carroll, Diahann; Martin Show, Tony
  - Martin, Steve see Three Girls Three
  - Martin Show, Tony see also The Music Scene
    - Travelin’ medley part I: Nov. 2, 1965, For Dean Martin, Stanley Holloway, and Bill Dana.; Includes: "A nightingale sang in Berkeley Square;" "The Road to Morocco." (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Mary Hartman, Mary Hartman (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Mateo, Pete & Beverly Layne/Layme
    - Corny (Box-folder 17/6)
    - I miss you so: July 27, 1970 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Just say I love you too much (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Sighs of the times (Box-folder 17/9)
    - Was I a fool/Was I a merry go round (Box-folder 17/10)
  - McKuen, Rod see also Yarborough, Glenn
    - Angela: April 18, 1973 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Angela additional parts: April 20, 1973 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Ballad of the sad young men: April 18, 1973 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Blessings of the day: March 9, 1973 (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Everyday that I may love: Stanyon Records (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Fiore serenade: March 7, 1975 (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Forty without fear: April 18, 1973 Forty without fear added parts (Box-folder 17/16)
    - A friend - My friend (Box-folder 17/17)
    - Guess I’d rather be in Colorado: Stanyon Records (Box-folder 17/18)
    - If: March 9, 1973 (Box-folder 17/19)
    - In the night: Feb. 10, 1972 (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Let me take you with me: Feb. 10, 1972 (Box-folder 17/21)
    - Lisa Bright and Dark: M-91 epilogue (Box-folder 17/22)
    - Love conquers all (Box-folder 17/23)
    - Manchester: Feb. 5, 1972 (Box-folder 17/24)
    - McKuen retrospective 73: April 18, 1973, Includes: "Oliver Twist;" "When my ship comes in;" "Happy is a boy;" "Come on back;" "Time after time;" "Tell me what I say." (Box-folder 17/25)
    - Neige sur liege: Stanyon Records (Box-folder 17/26)
    - Religious medley ‘73, Includes: "Give me that old time religion;" "Shake a hand;" "I’m saved." (Box-folder 17/27)
    - The sea gull: Stanyon Records (Box-folder 17/28)
    - Since you’ve asked: Stanyon Records (Box-folder 17/29)
    - Sunday: April 20, 1973 (Box-folder 17/30)
    - Thursday (Box-folder 17/31)
    - Time and distance added parts (Box-folder 17/32)
    - Today I found a friend: Stanyon Records (Box-folder 17/33)
    - Watch the roses grow: April 20, 1973 (Box-folder 17/34)
    - Will you love me, tomorrow?: March 7, 1975 (Box-folder 17/35)
  - McLeod [MacLeod], Gavin
    - Queen from Moline (Box-folder 18/1)
  - McRae, Carmen
    - Would you believe (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Meeza, Lee
    - After today (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Feelin’ good (Box-folder 18/4)
    - For once in my life (Box-folder 18/5)
    - House of the rising sun: Joey Bishop Show (Box-folder 18/6)
    - I’ve gotta be me: April 9, 1968 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - So what!: April 10, 1968 (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Something in your smile (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Stagger Lee Stagger Lee combo parts (Box-folder 18/10)
  - MGM Grand Hotel
    - Living curtain - fanfare; Living curtain #1; Living curtain #2; Living curtain #3; Living curtain #4 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Midler, Bette see Crosby, Bing
  - M.I.M. pilot
    - End title: M-702; Group jump: M-501; Last jump: M701; Bongo jump: M 401; Nancy’s walk: M-301 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Minnelli, Liza see also Baryshnikov on Broadway
    - As I in my chair (Box-folder 18/13)
    - The Circle: 1973 (Box-folder 18/14)
    - Dancin’ in the moonlight, rescore: May 1, 1973 (Box-folder 18/15)
    - I can see clearly (Box-folder 18/16)
    - I wanna listen to rag, Includes "Play a simple melody." (Box-folder 18/17)
    - Liza - Desi - opening, For Liza and Desi. (Box-folder 18/18)
    - Magic is the moonlight intro: May 4, 1973 (Box-folder 18/19)
    - One of a kind (Box-folder 18/20)
    - Overture, short (Box-folder 18/21)
    - [Play a] simple melody continued (Box-folder 18/22)
    - A quiet thing - new ending (Box-folder 18/23)
    - Shine on harvest moon (Box-folder 18/24)
    - Sing, sing, sing: April 1, 1973, For Liza and Desi. (Box-folder 18/25)
    - Le Temps (Box-folder 18/26)
    - Two of a kind, For Liza and Joel Grey. (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.
    - Liza: T.S.T.L.O. (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Mr. Wonderful: T.S.T.L.O. Liza/Sammy in Miami (Box-folder 19/3)
    - [One] T.S.T.L.O.: Liza and Sammy in Miami (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Razzle-dazzle bows, Arranged by Ralph Burns. (Box-folder 19/5)
    - This is the night - opening: Feb. 1, 1977, vaudeville, Includes: "I can do that." (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Minnelli, Liza and Goldie Hawn: tv special, George Schlatter prod., 1979
    - And all that jazz And all that jazz - reprise (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Bad girls pt. I Bad girls pt. II (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Guys and dolls vocal tag, Intro (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Y.M.C.A, Includes: "A foggy day." (Box-folder 19/10)
  - Miscellaneous cues [envelope 1], Includes: Hangin’ in; M-51 The plane; [Untitled]; Commercial billboard; Underscore #2/Opening titles; Feel like dancing reprise; Closing credits; M-43 The punch; Last underscore; [What I did for love]. (Box-folder 19/11)
  - Miscellaneous cues [envelope 2], Includes: M-13 Van transition; M-31 You’re not gonna have her; M-52 You know for sure; M-61 You can take him home; Face opener & closer; Scoreboard part I/2; Cake rock tv tag; #29 London intro; #30 Finale. (Box-folder 19/12)
  - Miscellaneous cues [envelope 3], Includes: M-2 Overture to silence; M3 Nautical nonsense; M-4 Cannon of love; M5 Shipload of love; M6 Hello Hollywood; M-7 Girl chowder; M-8 Jungle of love; M9 Lockjaw & clubfoot; M-10 Elka bong; M-11 Oasis of love; M-12 Silent button; M14 Schwab 1940's; M-15 Bridge Schwabs to Intro men; M-16 Intro g.w.t.h.; M-17 Bridge to screen test; M18 Swedish screen test; M-19 Hungarian; M-20 Italian screen test; M21 Bridge to 1980; M-22 Intro survive; M23/23a Bumper; M-24 Schwabs 60's; M-25 Schwabs to intro mus. ladies; M-26 Intro Ginny; M27 Ginny sc. I end; M28 Intro Ginny sc. II; M-29 Ginny sc. II end; M-30 Schwab’s 1980's; M-31 End Schwab’s - Good nites; Joe’s world; Tell me a few things.; Some of the above are arranged by Chris Boardman. (Box-folder 19/13-14)
  - Moonchild [1974 film]
    - [Miscellaneous cues], Includes: M-a main title; M-12 sketch time; M-13 stinker; Girls theme; M-14 just folks; M-32 frail beauty; M-61 Pope’s pomp; M-31; M-51 more catacomb; M-52 mad love; M-53 courtyard painting; M-62 the alchemist; M-71 the ceremony; M-72 wedded bliss; M-73/m74 loop/amen; M-81 throttled kid; M-92 ascending stairs; M-94. (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Morrow, Buddy
    - Almost like being in love: Tommy Dorsey orchestra, 1980 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - You’ll never know: Tommy Dorsey band (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Mr. Dugan: (T.A.T. prod.) tv - 79
    - Yankee doodle dandy (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Mr. Night
    - [Miscellaneous cues], Includes: Main title; Cues - from intro; Master rhythm. (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Muppets see Andrews, Julie
  - MTM Emmy clips
    - [Miscellaneous cues], Includes: M-11 main title; M-12 cold coffee; M-13 Mary’s bath. (Box-folder 20/6)
  - The Music Scene: ABC-TV see also King, B.B.; Wonder, Stevie
    - Battle hymn on and Battle hymn off, Sept. 23, 1969 (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Both sides now (Box-folder 20/8)
    - Capitol punishment score: Oct. 20, 1969, Composed by Byers. (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Documentary scene, Composed by Pat Williams. (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Documentary play off, Composed by Byers. (Box-folder 20/10)
    - [Give my] regards to Broadway, For Della Reese. (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Give the baby a birthday kiss for us: CBS promos, May 10, 1970 (Box-folder 20/12)
    - Great balls of fire, For Jerry Lee Lewis. (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Here I go again: Sept. 23, 1969, For Smokey Robinson & the Miracles. (Box-folder 20/14)
    - [Hooray for] Captain Spaulding on and off (Box-folder 20/15)
    - I left my heart in San Francisco off: Aug. 25, 1969 (Box-folder 20/16)
    - I’ll be your baby tonight: Oct. 30, 1969, For Bobby Sherman. (Box-folder 20/17)
    - It’s all right with me, For Tony Martin. (Box-folder 20/18)
    - Jean: Sept. 17, 1969, For Oliver. (Box-folder 20/19)
    - Little woman: Oct. 2, 1969, For Bobby Sherman. (Box-folder 20/20)
    - The look of love: Oct. 8, 1969, For Dusty Springfield; plus printed score. (Box-folder 20/21)
    - Make your own kind of music: Oct. 24, 1969 (Box-folder 20/22)
    - Maybellene: Oct. 15, 1969, For Chuck Berry. (Box-folder 20/23)
    - Memphis underground: Oct. 2, 1967, For Herbie Mann. (Box-folder 20/24)
    - Mickey’s monkey: Sept. 24, 1969, For Smokey Robinson & the Miracles. (Box-folder 20/25)
    - [My Cherie] (Box-folder 20/26)
    - My tailor is rich: Sept. 5, 1969, Composed by Byers. (Box-folder 20/27)
    - Oh what a night: Oct. 1, 1969, For the Dells. (Box-folder 20/28)
    - Placement info: June 14, 1970 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Placement 2-b: June 24, 1970, Printed copy. (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Rich Tailor - bridge and button, Composed by Byers. (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Roll over Beethoven: Oct. 15, 1969, For Chuck Berry. (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Same old something: Oct. 11, 1969, For Dusty Springfield. (Box-folder 21/4)
    - She even woke me up to say goodbye, For Jerry Lee Lewis. (Box-folder 21/5)
    - Since I met you baby: Oct. 6, 1969, For Sonny Jumps. (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Stravinsk bridge and button, Composed by Byers. (Box-folder 21/7)
    - The Sugar opera: Oct. 6, 1969 (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Sugar, sugar: Aug. 17, 1967 (Box-folder 21/9)
    - [Three] 3 music scene buttons: Sept. 12, 1969, Composed by Pat Williams. (Box-folder 21/10)
    - What’s the use of breaking up?: Oct. 2, 1969, For Jerry Butler. (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Nabors, Jim
    - I’ll begin again: Columbia (Box-folder 21/12)
    - Louisiana woman: Columbia (Box-folder 21/13)
    - Love one another: Columbia (Box-folder 21/14)
  - Never Steal Anything Wet: Executive Pictures
    - [Miscellaneous cues], Includes Reel 2 part 5; Reel 5 part 1; Reel 5 part 2; Reel 5 part 3; R6 p2; Reel 7 part 5. (Box-folder 21/15)
  - Newley, Anthony see also Hamlisch, Marvin and Jeffries, Fran
    - Newley overture, 1976 (Box-folder 21/16)
    - Opening cont.: Newley/Mancini, Starts at p. 5.; Includes "New York, New York;" "Lullaby of Broadway;" "Sidewalks of New York;" "Give my regards to Broadway;" "Autumn in New York;" "I happen to like New York." (Box-folder 21/17)
    - Pop goes the disco: vaudeville, 1978 (Box-folder 21/18)
    - Smile (Box-folder 21/19)
    - The story teller: vaudeville, 1977 (Box-folder 21/20)
    - Sweet beginning: Haddassah, 1975 (Box-folder 21/21)
    - Wouldn’t that be nice: vaudeville, 1977 (Box-folder 21/22)
  - Newton, Wayne see Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
  - Noel, Dick
    - [Dindi] Dindy (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Fred (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Shades of today: May 3, 1967 (Box-folder 22/3)
  - O’Connor, Carroll
    - Clothes make the girl (Box-folder 22/4)
    - It’s a man’s world: CBS special, 1973 (Box-folder 22/5)
  - Oliver see The Music Scene
  - One-A; One-B, Found attached to back of "Can we get together again." (Box-folder 22/6)
  - Opening (Box-folder 22/7)
  - The Osmonds see also ABC 25th anniversary
    - Donny hit medley, Feb. 20, 1971, Includes "Hey girl;" "Go away little girl." (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Lazy river: Osmond Brothers, Dec. 20, 1971 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Let the little girl dance: M.G.M. Fairfax (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Medley - Osmond Brothers, Sept. 19, 1972, Includes "Go away little girl." (Box-folder 22/11)
    - One bad apple: Osmond Brothers (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Rubber ball: M.G.M. Fairfax, May 3, 1972 (Box-folder 22/13)
    - That lovin’ feeling: Dec. 18, 1970 (Box-folder 22/14)
  - Owen, Michael
    - You and I (Box-folder 22/15)
  - Page, Patti
    - Don’t dream of anybody (but me) (Box-folder 22/16)
    - Don’t sleep in the subway: stage arrangement (Box-folder 22/17)
    - I can’t take it (Box-folder 22/18)
    - I can’t take my eyes off of you: stage arrangement (Box-folder 22/19)
    - I haven’t got anything better to do: stage arrangement (Box-folder 22/20)
  - Peck, Gregory see Ann-Margret
  - Peters, Bernadette
    - Broadway baby: vaudeville 1977, A medley of songs with the same title from Dames at Sea and Follies. (Box-folder 22/21)
    - Brussels: vaudeville 1977 (Box-folder 22/22)
    - A love story: vaudeville 1977 (Box-folder 22/23)
    - Love you didn’t do right by me: vaudeville 1977 (Box-folder 22/24)
  - Peterson, Oscar
    - Cheek to cheek: live tv 78, Oscar Peterson feature (Box-folder 22/25)
    - Pick yourself up, Includes "The Continental;" "Cheek to cheek." (Box-folder 22/26)
  - Prowse, Juliet
    - [Eighty] 80 m.p.h. thru beer can country, Composed by Gary McFarland. (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Opening 1977: vaudeville 1977, Includes "Razzle dazzle" and "All that jazz." (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Opening number, Arranged by Ralph Burns. (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Webb medley, For Richard Ryder.; Includes "Didn’t we." (Box-folder 23/4)
  - Prysock, Arthur
    - Tenderly: April 20, 1973 (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Radio City Music Hall Special: Smith-Hemion, 1978
    - Hallelujah (Box-folder 23/6)
    - To be a rockette, For Ann-Margret. (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Randall, Tony
    - Those wedding bells shall not ring out (Box-folder 23/8)
    - [Miscellaneous cues] Tony Randall #7354, Includes M12 Ruebher’s dates; M-21 Another way; M-21 Who cares? (Box-folder 23/9)
  - Raney, Sue
    - Better break it to me gently: Liberty Records (Box-folder 23/10)
    - Breathless: Liberty Records; Bows and Breathless reprise (Box-folder 23/11)
    - Breathless (Box-folder 23/12)
    - A certain misunderstanding: Liberty Records (Box-folder 23/13)
    - Color medley (Box-folder 23/14)
    - Didn’t we? medley: vaudeville arrangement, May 25, 1969, Includes "Didn’t we?;" "MacArthur Park." (Box-folder 23/15)
    - Does anybody here love me: Liberty Records (Box-folder 23/16)
    - Early morning blues and greens: Liberty Records (Box-folder 23/17)
    - [Five] 5 meanings of love (Box-folder 23/18)
    - For once in my life: vaudeville arrangement, May 8, 1969 (Box-folder 23/19)
    - Georgia boy: Liberty Records, July 13, 1967 (Box-folder 23/20)
    - Groovin’: Liberty Records, July 6, 1967 (Box-folder 23/21)
    - Have I stayed too long at the fair?: Liberty Records, July 6, 1967 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Holiday for strings: Liberty Records, July 6, 1967 (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Hope (Box-folder 24/3)
    - How about me?: vaudeville arrangement (Box-folder 24/4)
    - I can hear the music (the Carroll Chessman theme): Liberty Records, July 12, 1967 (Box-folder 24/5)
    - I can’t remember ever loving you (Box-folder 24/6)
    - I’ll get by: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/7)
    - It’s just a matter of time: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Know you opener, Includes "Getting to know you." (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Knowing when to leave: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/10)
    - Let me down easy (Box-folder 24/11)
    - A little help from my friends (Box-folder 24/12)
    - Live for life: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/13)
    - Love (Webster’s definition) (Box-folder 24/14)
    - Love me tender: Liberty Records, April 6, 1967 (Box-folder 24/15)
    - Once was a time I thought: Liberty Records, July 12, 1967 (Box-folder 24/16)
    - Open for biz: Liberty Records, July 13, 1967 (Box-folder 24/17)
    - Our day will come: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/18)
    - Raindrops keep falling [on my head]: vaudeville arrangement (Box-folder 24/19)
    - Soldier in the rain: Sept. 12, 1969 (Box-folder 24/20)
    - Sunday mornin’: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/21)
    - Sweet gentle love; Sweet gentle love overdub (Box-folder 24/22)
    - Take my word: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/23)
    - Vaya con dios: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/24)
    - Wait till the sun shines Willie (Box-folder 24/25)
    - Wait until dark: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/26)
    - We’ll be together again: Liberty Records, July 6, 1967 (Box-folder 24/27)
    - When oh when (Box-folder 24/28)
    - Where does love go/No one will ever know: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/29)
    - Where’s the love: Liberty Records, May 13, 1967 (Box-folder 24/30)
    - Windmills of your mind - [On the] Apple [tree] medley: vaudeville arrangement, May 5, 1969 (Box-folder 24/31)
    - Without me: Liberty Records (Box-folder 24/32)
  - Raff, Reneé
    - Among the stars, Parts only. (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Butterfly with hiccups: June 27, 1965, Parts laid in. (Box-folder 34/3)
    - He lied, Parts only. (Box-folder 34/4)
    - In the interim: June 27, 1965, Parts laid in. (Box-folder 34/5)
    - Jang pierewiet, Parts only. (Box-folder 34/6)
    - Let there be love, Parts only. (Box-folder 34/7)
    - Please don’t leave me: June 27, 1965, Parts laid in. (Box-folder 34/8)
    - Starting tomorrow: June 13, 1965, Parts laid in. (Box-folder 34/9)
  - Raw Satin see Ann-Margret
  - Rawls, Lou
    - Ellington medley (fix), Includes "Sophisticated lady;" "I got it bad;" "Mood indigo." (Box-folder 25/1)
  - Reddy, Helen
    - Dance in the old fashioned way (Box-folder 25/2)
    - Hospitality suite (Box-folder 25/3)
  - Reese, Della see also The Music Scene and Vaughan, Sarah
    - After the ball: Aug. 27, 1969 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Alexander’s ragtime band, Arranged by Pete Myers. (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Around the world: KHJ-TV, Sept. 17, 1969 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Baby won’t you please come home: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV (Box-folder 25/7)
    - Comes once in a lifetime: Della Reese Show KHJ (Box-folder 25/8)
    - Don’t blame me: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Oct. 20, 1969 (Box-folder 25/9)
    - Down with love: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Sept. 24, 1969 (Box-folder 25/10)
    - For you, Arranged by J. Hill. (Box-folder 25/11)
    - Give my regards to Broadway: Della Reese Show KHJ (Box-folder 25/12)
    - I can’t believe that you’re in love with me: KHJ, Dec. 10, 1969 (Box-folder 25/13)
    - I can’t stop loving you: channel #9 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - I had a ball, Arranged by Mike Barone or Bobby Bryant. (Box-folder 25/15)
    - I hadn’t anyone ‘till you: KHJ-TV, Printed copy. (Box-folder 25/16)
    - If you were the only boy: KHJ-TV (Box-folder 25/17)
    - It don’t mean a thing: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Sept. 5, 1969 (Box-folder 25/18)
    - I’ve told every little star: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV (Box-folder 25/19)
    - Just a gigolo: KHJ (Box-folder 25/20)
    - Let it snow: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Nov. 27, 1969 (Box-folder 25/21)
    - Light my fire: Della Reese Show, July 9, 1969 (Box-folder 25/22)
    - Love: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Oct. 25, 1969, Arranged by Yuriko S. Byers. (Box-folder 25/23)
    - Lush life: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Oct. 8, 1969 (Box-folder 25/24)
    - My favorite things: Della Reese Show (Box-folder 26/1)
    - My ship: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Nov. 1, 1969 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Nothing can stop me now!: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Oct. 20, 1969 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Sit down you’re rocking the boat: KHJ (Box-folder 26/4)
    - South of the border: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Oct. 8, 1969 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - A Sunday kind of love: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Nov. 17, 1969 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - Tangerine: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Nov. 1, 1969 (Box-folder 26/7)
    - This nearly was mine: KHJ (Box-folder 26/8)
    - Too close for comfort: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Oct. 17, 1969 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - The way you look tonight, Arranged by Mike Barone or Bobby Bryant. (Box-folder 26/10)
    - In the wee small hours: Della Reese Show KHJ-TV, Oct. 25, 1969 (Box-folder 26/11)
  - Reynolds, Debbie
    - Music and the mirror, Percussion, keyboard, vocal and violin parts laid in. (Box-folder 26/12)
  - Rich, Buddy see Clark, Dick
  - Robinson, Smokey and the Miracles see The Music Scene
  - Rodgers/Hart tv special, 1976